[{"id":1,"question":"What type of relationship is defined as one resource existing only if another parent resource exist-for example, pages in a book?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Partial`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`dependent`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`associative`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`linked`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":2,"question":"Which URL pattern is recommended when working with one resource and a collection of resources?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`/companies/{id} and/company`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`/company/{id} and/companies`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`/companies/{id} and/companies`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`/company/{id} and/company`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":3,"question":"When dealing with JSON web Tokens (JWTs), what is a claim?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`data in the token`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Ownership`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`a permission`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`and integer`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":4,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that knowledge and understanding obtained from one component of the API should be generally applicable elsewhere in the API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Uniform Interface`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Client-Server`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Stateless`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Chacheable`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":5,"question":"What would you enable to allow a browser on another site to make an AJAX request to your API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`HTTP`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`REST`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`OPTIONS`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`CORS`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":6,"question":"APIs commonly use webhooks to **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`notify other systems of an event`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`catch error faster`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`improve error logging`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`log additional data`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":7,"question":"What is the underlying goal of all APIs?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`to add new technologies to an organization's infrastructure.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`to share features and functionality with other system.`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`to move infrastructure to the cloud.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`to appease the latest digital transformation effort.`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":8,"question":"Which is a common command-line tool for using or exploring an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`bash`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`curl`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`ssh`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`powerShell`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":9,"question":"What is the modern specification for describing an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`OpenAPI (Swagger)`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`WADL`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`WSDL`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`OAuth`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":10,"question":"Which HTTP verb is normally used to update or create a resource in an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`SUBMIT`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`WRITE`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`POST`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`CREATE`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":11,"question":"What is one benefit of server-side caching in APIs?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Mobile app work better.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`It improves uptime.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`It offers better security.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`It reduce load on servers.`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":12,"question":"Your API resource does no allow deletion, and a client application attempted to delete the resource. What HTTP response code should you return?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`409 Conflict`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`400 Bad Request`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`406 Not Acceptable`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`405 Method Not Allowed`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":13,"question":"What is OpenID Connect?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`the new name for SAML 3.0`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`a modern replacement for API keys`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`an SSO competitor for OAuth 2.0`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":14,"question":"What is one benefit of GraphQl over REST approaches?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`flexible querying/responses`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`more stable APIs`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`compatible with more gateways`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`more secure by default`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":15,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that there should be no shared context?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Stateless`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Client-Server`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Uniform Interface`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Cacheable`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":16,"question":"What purpose does a User-Agent serve?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`It identifies the user ID.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`It identifies the client application or SDK.`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`It identifies if the API should expect a user authentication.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`It identifies if the API should accept microservice traffic.`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":17,"question":"If you were to add versioning by using the Accept and Content-Type header, what would be the correct format of the header value?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`application/json`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`application/json_version2`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`text/html`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`application/vnd.myapp.v2+json`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":18,"question":"What is one benefit that OAuth provides over an API key approach?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`A token is encrypted.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`A token is encoded.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`A token is scoped to the use case.`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`A token can be shared between systems.`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":19,"question":"The ability to execute the same API request over and over again without changing the resource's state is an example of _.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`stateless architecture`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`idempotency`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`a uniform interface`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`cacheability`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":20,"question":"What component can you use to wrap legacy architectures or protocols into a REST interface for easier consumption and integration?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`API proxy`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`API gateway`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`OpenAPI`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`OAuth authorization server`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":21,"question":"What protection does a JSON Web Token (JWT) offer to mitigate tampering with its contents?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`transport over SSL`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`encrypted payload`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`a signature`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`encoded payload`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":22,"question":"What OAuth term is used to represent permissions?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`token`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`scope`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`claim`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`back channel`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":23,"question":"What additional type of token would you see when using OpenID Connect?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`ID token`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`refresh token`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`access token`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`auth code token`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":24,"question":"What should you add to a Cache-Control response header to specify that a response should not be stored in an intermediary cache?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`no-proxy`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`client-only`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`restricted`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`private`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":25,"question":"Which OAuth grant type can support a refresh token?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Authorization Code Grant`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Client Credentials Grant`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Implicit Grant`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Authentication Grant`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":26,"question":"Using OAuth, what scope would you request for write access to the API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`It varies from API to API.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`admin`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`write`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`read-write`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":27,"question":"Which property would you use to include subresources directly into a JSON document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`_embedded`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`resources`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`subresources`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`_links`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":28,"question":"What is the best way to track SDK and version usage?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`tracking downloads`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Accept headers`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`user agents`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`polling users`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":29,"question":"Which REST constraint allows for the presence of caching, routing, and other systems between the client and server?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Layered System`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Stateless`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Client-Server`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Cacheable`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":30,"question":"Which content is best to include in your documentation?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`your tech stack`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`reasoning for your naming schema`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`your mission statement`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`sample code`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":31,"question":"What metric tracks overall availability for your API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Response Time`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Time to First Hello World`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`TTL`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Uptime`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":32,"question":"What is the recommended method and URL pattern for retrieving a specific user?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`GET /user/{id}`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`GET /users/{id}`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`GET /user?id={id}`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`GET /users?id={id}`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":33,"question":"What is the purpose of a link relation?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`to describe relationships between resources or actions`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`to describe subresources related to the current one`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`to link two resources together`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`to describe a resource and its purpose`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":34,"question":"When building SDKs, which languages should you support?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Java, Javascript, and .NET","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"and you can support","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"PHP, Python, and Go","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the languages that your target users use","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":35,"question":"Which property would you use to include references to other resources in a JSON document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`resources`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`_embedded`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`subresources`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`_links`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":36,"question":"What is OAuth?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"an authorization framework for granted delegated access","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"an approach to single sign-on for APIs","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a method for API authentication","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"HTTP Basic Authentication 2.0","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":37,"question":"What should your API documentation describe?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"JSON","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"HTTP","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"common use cases","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"your tech stack","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":38,"question":"What is the purpose of an OAuth refresh token?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"to share user profile information","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"to update an API configuration","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"to keep a web session active","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"to retrieve an access token","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":39,"question":"What is Time to First Hello World?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"how long it takes to start a new programming language","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"how long it takes to install your SDK","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"how long it takes to read your documentation","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":40,"question":"Which response header tells the client and intermediaries that the response is not to be cached anywhere?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Cache-State: none","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Expires:-1","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cache-Control: no-cache","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cache-Control: no-store","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":41,"question":"What component hides the distinctions or boundaries between various microservices from end-client applications?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`API gateway`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`API logging `","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`a layered system `","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`API proxy`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":42,"question":"The textbook approach to api versioning is to use **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`common knowledge`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`URLs`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`no versioning`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`the Accept header`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":43,"question":"Which is the most secure method to transmit an API key?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`URL parameter`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Authorization header`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Base64 encoding`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Basic Auth`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":44,"question":"Within Oauth, what component validates the user's identity?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`client`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`not specified`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`authorization server`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`resource server`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":45,"question":"API traffic that is entirely internal to your organization is normally called _?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`inbound traffic`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`north-south traffic `","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`internal traffic `","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`east-west traffic`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":46,"question":"What is the best approach for requesting JSON instead of XML from an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Add .json to the URL.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`APIs do not use XML.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Use the Content-Type header.`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Use the Accept header.`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":47,"question":"When a user attempts to access a record that is not their own, which HTTP response code is the most appropriate?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`403`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`404`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`401`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`405`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":48,"question":"Which is a benefit of using an API gateway?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`HTTP verbs`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`JSON payloads`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`HTTP response codes`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`rate limiting/throttling`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":49,"question":"API testing must be treated as **_**?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`red team testing`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`white box testing`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`blue box testing`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`black box testing`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":50,"question":"Which HTTP verb is used in a CORS preflight request?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`PUT`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`POST`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`GET`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`OPTIONS`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":51,"question":"Which response header will tell the client that the response is cached for 1 minute ?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Expires: 1 minute`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Cache-Control: max-age=60`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Expires: 1 January 2020`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Cache-Expires: max-age=60`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":52,"question":"What is the concept that allows an API client to explore an API via links embedded in payloads?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`hypermedia`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`link relations`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`parsing`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`browsing`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":53,"question":"Which HTTP response code describes a new resource as created successfully?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`200`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`201`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`204`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`202`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":54,"question":"Which is an example of Code on Demand?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"AWS Lambda","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"downloading open-source software","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Serverless","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"JavaScript on a webpage","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":55,"question":"Which URL pattern should you follow for accessing a subresource attached to a specific resource?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"/companies/employees/{companyId}/{employeeId}","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"/company/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"/companies/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"/companies/{companyId}/employee/{employeeId}","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":56,"question":"Which REST constraint essentially prohibits the use of cookies?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Stateless","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Cacheable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Layered System","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Uniform Interface","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":57,"question":"Which HTTP verb is used to delete a resource?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"FLUSH","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DELETE","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"CLEAR","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"DESTROY","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":58,"question":"Which verb is _not_ considered idempotent?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"DELETE","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"GET","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"PUT","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"POST","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":59,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that each request should stand on its own and not have a specific required order?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Uniform Interface","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Cacheable","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Stateless","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Client-Server","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":60,"question":"When you get a 429 code, what should you do next?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Check you JSON structure.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Check the API uptime status.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Slow down your requests.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Check you API key.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":61,"question":"When exploring record sets, what is the best approach for pagination?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"date-based filtering","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"next/previous cursors","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"page size and filters","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"database IDs","answer":false,"code":false}]}]